https://hbu.edu/university-policies/privacy-policy/

Web Privacy Statement
Houston Baptist University (HBU) is devoted to safeguarding the privacy of personal information; however at times we may share information gathered from our web servers. Since we are a private institution, some information collected from this web site, including summary server log information, emails and information collected from web-based form, may be subject to public information requests under the Texas Public Information Act (TPIA). This means that while we do not share information, in some instances we may be required by Open Records law to discharge information.
Student directory information is routinely requested by vendors through the TPIA. Students have the option of excluding their personal information from the directory during registration.
HBU fully complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which disallows the release of educational records without the student’s consent.
The HBU web consists of several web servers. Some servers hosted by HBU may embrace different privacy statements as their specific needs require. If another HBU web server has a privacy statement that is different from this statement, that policy will be posted on their site. The HBU web site encompasses links to external web sites; however HBU is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external web links.
Information We Gather
The following information is collected and stored automatically from all users accessing the HBU web site to browse or download information:
Internet address of computer being used
Web pages requested
Referring web page
Date and time
Type of web browser being used
This information is used to create summary statistics which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest to users, determining technical specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. This information is not reported or used in any means that would disclose personally identifiable information, and will not be released to outside third parties unless legally obligated.
Terms and Conditions of Use
Acceptance of terms and use and amendments
Each time you use or cause access to the HBU web site, you agree to be bound by these terms of use, as amended from time to time with or without notice to you. In addition, if you are using a particular service on this web site or accessed through this web site, you will be subject to any rules or guidelines pertinent to those services. Please read the site’s privacy policy, which is comprised within these terms of use.
Your responsibilities and registration obligations
In order to use this web site or certain parts of it, you may be required to register for a user account on this web site. In this case, you agree to provide truthful information when requested. By registering for a user account, you explicitly agree to this site’s terms of use.
Privacy policy
Registration data and other personally identifiable information that the site may collect is subject to the terms of the web privacy policy. HBU is committed to ensuring the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information.
Registration and password
You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, and you will be responsible for all usage of your user account and/or user name, whether authorized or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify HBU of any unauthorized use of your user account, user name or password.
Disclaimer of Warranties
You understand and agree that your use of this web site and of any services or content provided (the “service”) is at your own risk. Services and content are provided to you “as is,” and HBU expressly disclaims all warranties of any kind, either implied or expressed, including but not limited to warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.HBU makes no warranty, either implied or expressed, that any part of the service will be uninterrupted, error/virus-free, timely, secure, accurate, reliable, or of any quality, nor is it warranted either implicitly or expressly that any content is safe in any manner for download. You understand and agree that neither HBU nor any participant in the service provides professional advice of any kind and that any advice or any other information obtained via this web site may be used exclusively at your own risk and that HBU will not be held liable in any way.
Some jurisdictions may not allow disclaimers of implied warranties, and certain statements in the above disclaimer may not apply to you as regards implied warranties; the other terms and conditions remain enforceable notwithstanding.
Limitation of Liability
You specifically recognize and agree that HBU will not be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages; this includes, but is not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses (even if HBU has been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from the following:
i. the use of services or the inability to use services,
ii. the cost of obtaining substitute goods and/or services resulting from any transaction entered into on through services,
iii. unauthorized access to or alteration of your data transmissions,
iv. statements by any third party or conduct of any third party using services, or
v. any other matter relating to services.
In some jurisdictions, it is not permitted to limit liability and, therefore, such limitations may not apply to you.
University PoliciesEmployeesAlcohol PolicyDrug PolicySexual Assault PolicySexual Harassment PolicyUniversity Facilities PoliciesSmoke Free Campus PolicyTrademark Licensing PolicyCopyright Infringement PolicyStudent Non-Discriminatory PolicyEvent Coverage ReleaseHBU Title IXPrivacy PolicyGeneral Data Privacy Regulation (GDPR)
Tuition and Aid
Request Information
Visit Campus
Apply Now
Contact Us Houston Baptist University
7502 Fondren Rd
Houston, TX 77074
(281) 649-3000
